But	O
he	O
says	O
Pakistan	B-gpe
is	O
not	O
ready	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
nuclear	O
scientist	OO
Abdul	B-per
Qadeer	I-per
Khan	I-perO
available	O
for	O
direct	O
questioning	O
over	O
his	O
sale	O
of	O
nuclear	O
parts	O
and	O
secrets	O
Iran	B-gpeO
Libya	B-gpe
North	B-gpe
Korea	I-gpe
Pakistani	B-gpe
Washington	B-geo
Khan	B-per
2004	B-time
Islamabad	B-geoO
Pakistan	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
Army	B-org
Wednesday	B-time
Halliburton	B-org
U.S.	B-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
Halliburton	B-org
services	OO
communication	OO
Halliburton	B-org
re-bidding	OO
Asia	B-org
Pacific	I-org
Economic	I-org
Cooperation	I-org
Business	I-org
Advisory	I-org
Council	I-org
APEC	B-org
September	B-time
8	I-time
9	B-time
VOA	B-org
Nancy-Amelia	B-per
Collins	I-per
Sydney	B-geo
Energy	OO
security	OO
change	OO
World	B-org
Trade	I-org
Organization	I-org
negotiations	OO
APEC	B-org
Business	I-org
Advisory	I-org
Council	I-orgO
ABAC	B-org
Tim	B-per
Harcourt	I-perO
Australian	B-org
Trade	I-org
Commission	I-orgO
ABAC	B-org
logjams	OO
obstacles	OO
improve	OO
Harcourt	B-per
ABAC	B-org
ABAC	B-org
APEC	B-org
1995	B-time
APEC	B-org
sectors	OO
ABAC	B-org
practices	OO
Harcourt	B-perO
Australian	B-org
Trade	I-org
Commission	I-orgO
ABAC	B-org
quarantine	OO
region	OO
Harcourt	B-per
security	OO
immigration	OO
customs	OO
ABAC	B-org
APEC	B-org
APEC	B-org
Saturday	B-time
Sudan	B-gpe
Darfur	B-geoO
Foreign	B-per
Minister	I-per
Mustafa	I-per
Osman	I-per
Ismail	I-per
Sudanese	B-gpe
April	B-time
cease-fire	OO
Mr.	B-per
Ismail	I-per
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
African	B-org
Union	I-org
Khartoum	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
weeks	OO
AU	B-org
Sudanese	B-gpe
April	B-time
Saturday	B-timeO
AU	B-org
Darfur	B-geo
Sudanese	B-gpe
South	B-geo
Darfur	I-geo
Labado	B-geo
Khartoum	B-gpe
South	B-geo
Darfur	I-geo
Indonesian	B-gpe
October	B-time
1	I-time
Bali	B-geo
Indonesian	B-gpe
Wednesday	B-time
Bali	B-geo
Java	B-geo
Bali	B-geo
Australian	B-gpe
French	B-gpe
Cholily	B-per
Indonesia	B-geo
Azahari	B-per
bin	I-per
Husin	I-per
Indonesian	B-gpe
Azahari	B-per
bin	I-per
Husin	I-per
Bali	B-geo
2002	B-time
Bali	B-geo
Roman	B-org
Catholic	I-org
Mogadishu	B-geoO
Somalia	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
Pope	B-per
Benedict	I-per
nun	OO
Sister	B-per
Leonella	I-per
Sgorbati	I-perO
Mogadishu	B-geo
Rome	B-geoO
Vatican	B-org
event	OO
Mogadishu	B-geo
Byzantine	B-per
Prophet	B-per
Muhammed	I-per
Pakistani	B-gpe
day	OO
Saturday	B-time
Orakzai	B-geo
region	OO
Taliban	B-org
South	B-geo
Waziristan	I-geo
Pakistani	B-gpe
Orakzai	B-geo
Taliban	B-org
far	OO
Thursday	B-time
Friday	B-timeO
Orakzai	B-geo
northwest	OO
Saturday	B-time
Kurram	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
U.S.	B-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
Taleban	B-org
Saturday	B-time
Uruzgan	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
others	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
soldier	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Paktika	B-geo
Separately	OO
British	B-gpe
Saturday	B-time
Mazar-e-Sharif	B-geo
Taleban	B-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
Russian	B-gpe
nation	OO
Moscow	B-geo
exposure	OO
Russia	B-geo
Itar-Tass	B-org
Russia	B-geoO
Baltic	B-geo
states	I-geo
Lithuania	B-geoO
Latvia	B-geo
Estonia	B-geoO
Moscow	B-geo
Vietnam	B-geo
Vietnamese	B-gpe
week	OO
Vietnam	B-geo
Ninh	B-gpe
Binh	I-gpe
Thursday	B-time
Vietnam	B-geo
death	OO
World	B-org
Health	I-org
Organization	I-org
2003	B-time
cases	OO
103	OO
Indonesia	B-geo
Somalia	B-geo
Mogadishu	B-geoO
Ethiopian	B-gpe
Wednesday	B-time
Ethiopian	B-gpe
Defense	B-org
Ministry	I-org
Mogadishu	B-geo
Ethiopian	B-gpe
Ethiopia	B-gpe
Somalia	B-geo
December	B-time
Somalia	B-gpe
Islamist	B-org
African	B-org
Union	I-org
Somalia	B-geo
Ethiopian	B-gpe
forces	OO
Addis	B-gpe
Ababa	I-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Ahmed	B-per
Qureia	I-per
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
reporters	OO
Qureia	B-per
Israeli	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ehud	I-per
Olmert	I-per
Palestinian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
November	B-timeO
U.S.	B-gpe
President	B-per
George	I-per
Bush	I-per
Qureia	B-per
Wednesday	B-time
Israel	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Bush	I-per
West	B-geo
Bank	I-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Major	B-per
General	I-per
Udi	I-per
Adam	I-per
Northern	B-org
Command	I-org
Wednesday	B-timeO
General	B-per
Adam	I-per
possible	OO
Adam	B-per
Hezbollah	B-org
Lebanon	B-geo
Lebanon	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Adam	B-per
chief	OO
Lieutenant	B-per
General	I-per
Dan	I-per
Halutz	I-perO
Pakistan	B-gpe
Institute	B-org
for	I-org
Science	I-org
and	I-org
International	I-org
Security	I-org
Khushab	B-geo
Punjab	B-geo
plutonium	OO
reports	OO
Pakistan	B-gpe
Pakistan	B-geo
Foreign	B-org
Ministry	I-org
Tasnim	B-per
Aslam	I-per
constructed	OO
Khushab	B-geo
American	B-org
Diabetes	I-org
Association	I-org
early	OO
VOA	B-org
June	B-per
Soh	I-per
Amy	B-per
Katz	I-per
Cuba	B-gpe
Panama	B-gpe
relations	OO
Havana	B-gpe
Panama	B-gpe
City	I-gpe
Cuban	B-gpe
President	B-per
Fidel	I-per
Castro	I-per
consulates	OO
Friday	B-time
Panamanian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Martin	I-per
Torrijos	I-per
Cuban	B-gpe
Vice	B-per
President	I-per
Carlos	I-per
Lage	I-per
San	B-geo
Jose	I-geoO
Costa	B-geo
Rica	I-geoO
Organization	B-org
of	I-org
American	I-org
States	I-org
Cuba	B-gpe
Panama	B-gpe
August	B-timeO
Panamanian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Mireya	I-per
Moscoso	I-perO
office	OO
men	OO
Cuba	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Castro	I-per
2000	B-time
Panama	B-geo
City	I-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
Israel	B-geo
Palestinian	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Gaza	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
June	B-time
Palestinians	B-gpe
Sunday	B-timeO
Palestinian	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ismail	I-per
Haniyeh	I-per
Israel	B-gpe
Arab	B-gpe
Palestinians	B-gpe
Israel	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Hamas	B-org
Fatah	B-org
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
U.S.	B-geo
Chrysler	B-org
Mexico	B-geo
Saltillo	B-obj
Friday	B-timeO
Mexican	B-gpe
President	B-per
Felipe	I-per
Calderon	I-per
Chrysler	B-org
Mexico	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Calderon	I-per
Mexico	B-gpe
Chrysler	B-org
Pentastar	B-obj
V-6	I-obj
Chrysler	B-objO
Dodge	B-objO
Jeep	B-obj
Ram	B-obj
Mexican	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
Merck	B-org
Vioxx	B-obj
New	B-geo
Jersey	I-geo
Merck	B-org
Vioxx	B-org
Merck	B-org
Merck	B-org
Merck	B-org
Vioxx	B-obj
Thursday	B-time
Vioxx	B-obj
first	OO
Merck	B-org
Vioxx	B-obj
Merck	B-org
Nicole	B-per
Ritchie	I-per
ABC	B-org
News	I-org
Dianne	B-per
Sawyer	I-perO
The	B-obj
Simple	I-obj
Life	I-obj
boyfriend	OO
Joel	B-per
Madden	I-per
Good	B-org
Charlotte	I-org
Ritchie	B-per
wrong	OO
driving	OO
would	OO
n't	OO
August	B-time
2	I-time
3	B-time
Good	B-obj
Morning	I-obj
America	I-objO
August	B-time
3	I-time
20/20	B-obj
U.S.	B-gpe
Senator	B-per
John	I-per
Warner	I-per
Virginia	B-geoO
Iraq	B-geoO
2009	B-time
Warner	B-per
University	B-org
of	I-org
Virginia	I-org
Friday	B-time
2008	B-time
Senate	B-org
Armed	I-org
Services	I-org
Committee	I-org
President	B-per
Bush	I-per
Iraq	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Bush	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
Senate	B-org
Senate	B-org
office	OO
Navy	B-org
U.S.	B-gpe
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
December	B-time
Indian	B-geo
Ocean	I-geo
U.N.	B-org
Food	B-org
and	I-org
Agricultural	I-org
Organization	I-org
FAO	B-org
FAO	B-org
Indonesia	B-geoO
Maldives	B-geoO
Somalia	B-geoO
Sri	B-geo
Lanka	I-geo
Thailand	B-geo
Indonesia	B-geo
flu	OO
2003	B-time
Bekasi	B-geoO
Jakarta	B-geo
Tuesday	B-time
Monday	B-timeO
Jakarta	B-geo
week	OO
Tangerang	B-geo
poultry	OO
Thailand	B-gpe
Islamic	B-org
Thailand	B-geo
Malaysia	B-geo
Thai	B-gpe
Deputy	B-per
Interior	I-per
Minister	I-per
Sutham	I-per
Saengprathum	I-per
Malaysia	B-geo
Kelantan	B-geo
state	OO
Thailand	B-geo
Malaysia	B-gpe
photos	OO
Bangkok	B-gpe
Thai	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Thaksin	I-per
Shinawatra	I-per
Malaysia	B-geoO
Indonesia	B-geo
Thailand	B-geo
Malaysia	B-gpe
Indonesia	B-gpe
Bangkok	B-gpe
Muslims	B-org
Indonesia	B-geo
Malaysia	B-geo
Chinese	B-gpe
Shanghai	B-geo
Saturday	B-timeO
Japanese	B-gpe
rocks	OO
Shanghai	B-geo
Japan	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
Security	I-org
Council	I-org
Tokyo	B-gpe
Beijing	B-geoO
State	B-per
Councilor	I-per
Tang	I-per
Jiaxuan	I-per
Xinhua	B-org
China	B-gpe
Japan	B-geo
Foreign	B-per
Minister	I-perO
Nobutaka	B-per
Machimura	I-perO
Sunday	B-time
Beijing	B-geo
Chinese	B-gpe
counterpart	OO
Li	B-per
Zhaoxing	I-perO
2012	B-event
Summer	I-event
Olympics	I-event
London	B-geo
Games	B-event
way	OO
waste	OO
Olympic	B-org
Delivery	I-org
Authority	I-org
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Tony	I-per
Blair	I-per
London	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
year	OO
London	B-gpe
July	B-time
of	I-time
2005	I-time
Wednesday	B-time
Games	B-event
China	B-geo
China	B-geo
2008	B-event
Olympic	I-event
China	B-gpe
Sam	B-per
Beattie	I-per
Sichuan	B-geo
British	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
NATO	B-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
NATO	B-org
Kandahar	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
NATO	B-org
south	OO
NATO	B-org
Taleban	B-org
Kandahar	B-geo
Operation	B-event
Medusa	I-event
Taleban	B-org
stability	OO
Sri	B-geo
Lankan	B-gpe
Tamil	B-org
Friday	B-time
Colombo	B-geoO
Dharmeratnam	B-per
Sivaram	I-per
TamilNet	B-org
Web	B-obj
Sri	B-gpe
Lanka	I-gpe
english	B-obj
newspaper	OO
Daily	B-obj
Mirror	I-obj
Mr.	B-per
Sivaram	I-per
Web	B-obj
Sri	B-org
Lankan	B-geo
Tamil	B-org
Tiger	I-org
Mr.	B-per
Sivaram	I-perO
2001	B-timeO
Japan	B-gpe
North	B-gpe
Korea	I-gpe
Japanese	B-gpe
Monday	B-time
Beijing	B-geo
November	B-time
North	B-gpe
Korea	I-gpe
Japan	B-gpe
North	B-gpe
Korea	I-gpe
Tokyo	B-gpe
Pyongyang	B-gpe
North	B-gpe
Korea	I-gpe
North	B-gpe
Japanese	B-gpe
1970s	B-time
1980s	B-time
Iraq	B-geo
Iraqi	B-gpe
Saddam	B-per
Hussein	I-per
Human	B-org
Rights	I-org
Watch	I-orgO
Thursday	B-timeO
Iraqi	B-gpe
2003	B-time
Iraq	B-geo
Associated	B-org
Press	I-org
U.S.	B-gpe
Defense	B-org
Department	I-org
Saddam	B-per
Hussein	I-per
July	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
crimes	OO
Egypt	B-gpe
World	B-org
Health	I-org
Organization	I-org
Egyptian	B-gpe
WHO	B-org
Egyptians	B-gpe
Egypt	B-geo
Asia	B-geo
U.N.	B-org
Iraq	B-gpe
Saddam	B-per
Hussein	I-per
U.N.	B-org
U.S.	B-gpe
Federal	B-org
Reserve	I-org
Chairman	B-per
Paul	I-per
Volcker	I-per
program	OO
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Security	I-org
Council	I-org
U.S.	B-gpe
government-funded	B-org
alHurra	B-obj
station	OO
Mr.	B-per
Volcker	I-per
Saddam	B-per
estimates	OO
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Gulf	B-event
War	I-event
Iraq	B-gpe
Iraqi	B-gpe
Kyrgyzstan	B-gpe
Justice	B-org
Ministry	I-org
people	OO
Tynychbek	B-per
Akmatbayev	I-perO
Bishkek	B-geo
Interior	B-per
Minister	I-per
Murat	I-per
Sutalinov	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Akmatbayev	I-per
Wednesday	B-time
Kyrgyz	B-gpe
prison	OO
Bishkek	B-geoO
Thursday	B-time
Western	B-geo
Europe	I-geo
Iraq	B-geo
plane	OO
France	B-gpe
Aigle	B-org
Azur	I-org
airline	OO
Charles	B-obj
De	I-obj
Gaulle	I-obj
Paris	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
Baghdad	B-obj
International	I-obj
Airport	I-obj
Sunday	B-time
ceremonial	OO
French	B-gpe
passengers	OO
French	B-gpe
Foreign	B-per
Trade	I-per
Minister	I-per
Anne-Marie	I-per
Idrac	I-perO
France	B-gpe
Iraq	B-gpe
Paris	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Aigle	B-org
Azur	I-org
Baghdad	B-geo
Etihad	B-org
Emirates	B-org
airlines	I-orgO
United	B-geo
Arab	I-geo
Emirates	I-geoO
Baghdad	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
January	B-time
Labor	B-org
Department	I-org
Friday	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
report	OO
American	B-gpe
January	B-time
Department	B-org
of	I-org
Labor	I-org
week	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
rate	OO
Venezuelan	B-gpe
President	B-per
Hugo	I-per
Chavez	I-per
Colombia	B-gpe
United	B-gpe
States	I-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Chavez	I-per
Sunday	B-time
Mr.	B-per
Chavez	I-per
Colombian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Alvaro	I-per
Uribe	I-per
Friday	B-time
meeting	OO
Colombian	B-gpe
Defense	B-per
Minister	I-per
Juan	I-per
Manuel	I-per
Santos	I-per
Venezuela	B-gpe
Sunday	B-timeO
Mr.	B-per
Chavez	I-per
President	B-per
Uribe	I-per
March	B-time
Colombia	B-gpe
Ecuador	B-geo
Venezuela	B-gpe
Colombian	B-gpe
China	B-gpe
U.S.	B-gpe
Chinese	B-gpe
freedom	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
China	B-gpe
Wednesday	B-timeO
U.S.	B-org
Commission	I-org
on	I-org
International	I-org
Religious	I-org
Freedom	I-org
China	B-gpe
freedom	OO
Saturday	B-time
Chinese	B-gpe
Foreign	B-org
Ministry	I-org
Liu	B-per
Jianchao	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
Chinese	B-gpe
U.S	B-gpe
China	B-gpe
Liu	B-per
China	B-gpe
Chinese	B-gpe
law	OO
China	B-gpe
churches	OO
President	B-per
Bush	I-per
criminals	OO
pardons	OO
Monday	B-timeO
embezzlement	OO
government	OO
wildlife	OO
Monday	B-time
actions	OO
Mr.	B-per
Bush	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
powers	OO
White	B-org
House	I-org
basis	OO
Uganda	B-gpe
Lord	B-org
's	I-org
Resistance	I-org
Army	I-org
Friday	B-time
LRA	B-org
Saturday	B-time
Sudan	B-geo
However	OO
Joseph	B-per
Kony	I-per
Kony	B-per
LRA	B-org
International	B-org
Criminal	I-org
Court	I-org
LRA	B-org
Uganda	B-geo
Roger	B-per
Federer	I-per
Australian	B-event
Open	I-event
Swiss	B-gpe
Wednesday	B-time
German	B-gpe
Tommy	B-per
Haas	I-per
Kooyong	B-event
Classic	I-event
Melbourne	B-geo
tournament	OO
Association	B-obj
of	I-obj
Tennis	I-obj
Professionals	I-obj
Tour	I-obj
Haas	B-per
03-Jun	OO
06-Apr	OO
Federer	B-per
Australian	B-event
Open	I-eventO
Monday	B-time
European	B-org
Space	I-org
Agency	I-org
Saturn	B-geo
Titan	B-geo
Germany	B-geo
Friday	B-time
Huygens	B-obj
Cassini	B-obj
Saturn	B-geo
Friday	B-time
Huygens	B-obj
American	B-gpeO
European	B-geo
Italian	B-gpe
Earth	B-geo
Ugandan	B-gpe
Kizza	B-per
Besigye	I-per
bail	OO
Dr.	B-per
Besigye	I-per
Kampala	B-geo
Monday	B-time
Uganda	B-gpe
Dr.	B-per
Besigye	I-per
November	B-timeO
President	B-per
Yoweri	I-per
Museveni	I-per
Dr.	B-per
Besigye	I-per
Ugandan	B-gpe
High	B-org
Court	I-org
Judge	OO
John	B-per
Bosco	I-per
Katutsi	I-perO
High	B-org
Court	I-org
Dr.	B-per
Besigye	I-per
charges	OO
Monday	B-time
charges	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
President	B-per
Barack	I-per
Obama	I-per
American	B-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Obama	I-per
White	B-obj
House	I-obj
Rose	I-obj
Garden	I-obj
Monday	B-time
African-American	B-gpe
woman	OO
Regina	B-per
Benjamin	I-perO
U.S.	B-gpe
Surgeon	B-per
General	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Obama	I-per
Democrats	B-org
House	B-org
of	I-org
Representatives	I-org
Americans	B-gpe
World	B-org
Bank	I-org
Washington	B-geo
African	B-gpe
Latin	B-gpe
American	I-gpe
World	B-org
Bank	I-org
President	B-per
Paul	I-per
Wolfowitz	I-per
plan	OO
July	B-time
July	B-time
G-8	B-org
countries	OO
Africa	B-geo
World	B-org
Bank	I-org
Benin	B-gpeO
Bolivia	B-gpeO
Burkina	B-gpe
Faso	I-gpeO
Ethiopia	B-gpeO
Ghana	B-gpeO
Guyana	B-gpeO
Honduras	B-gpeO
Madagascar	B-gpeO
Mali	B-gpeO
Mozambique	B-gpeO
Nicaragua	B-gpeO
Niger	B-gpeO
Rwanda	B-gpeO
Senegal	B-gpeO
Tanzania	B-gpeO
Uganda	B-gpe
Zambia	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Tehran	B-geo
Tuesday	B-time
Wednesday	B-time
holiday	OO
Iranian	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Press	B-org
TV	I-org
Tehran	B-geo
Air	B-org
Quality	I-org
Control	I-org
Company	I-org
Saudi	B-geo
Arabia	I-geo
Iraq	B-geoO
capital	OO
Baghdad	B-geo
deserts	OO
midnight	B-time
Israelis	B-gpe
Tel	B-geo
Aviv	I-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
Ramallah	B-geo
responsible	OO
Mr.	B-per
Abbas	I-per
Israeli	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ariel	I-per
Sharon	I-per
Egypt	B-geo
Indonesian	B-gpe
Russia	B-gpe
Biak	B-geo
Papua	B-geo
New	I-geo
Guinea	I-geo
Indonesian	B-gpe
equator	OO
Earth	B-geo
June	B-time
Indonesian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Susilo	I-per
Bambang	I-per
Yudhoyono	I-per
Moscow	B-geo
Algerian	B-gpe
Monday	B-time
France	B-geo
Paris	B-geo
1995	B-time
Rachid	B-per
Ramda	I-per
Paris	B-geo
convicted	OO
Ramda	B-per
France	B-geo
Ramda	B-per
London	B-geo
Algerian	B-gpe
Armed	B-org
Islamic	I-org
Group	I-org
British	B-gpe
Ramda	B-per
1995	B-time
France	B-geo
Monday	B-time
trial	OO
Ramda	B-per
Paris	B-geo
subway	OO
July	B-time
25	I-timeI-time
1995	I-time
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Sudanese	B-gpe
Central	B-gpe
African	I-gpe
Republic	I-gpe
U.N.	B-org
U.N.	B-org
deal	OO
Wednesday	B-timeO
Sudanese	B-gpe
CAR	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
Sudan	B-gpe
April	B-time
Sudan	B-gpe
Sudan	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
Sudanese	B-gpe
Democratic	B-gpe
Republic	I-gpe
of	I-gpe
Congo	I-gpeO
Congolese	B-gpe
Sudan	B-gpe
Japan	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
Yu	B-per
Hagino	I-perO
23	OO
scene	OO
Uji	B-geo
Omar	B-per
Bakri	I-per
Mohammed	I-per
Europe	B-geo
French	B-gpe
Monday	B-timeO
Mr.	B-per
Bakri	I-per
Muslims	B-org
Europe	B-geoO
Downing	B-obj
Street	I-objO
Britain	B-gpe
Beirut	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Bakri	I-per
British	B-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Bakri	I-per
British	B-gpe
July	B-time
7	I-time
London	B-geo
Muslim	B-org
France	B-obj
3	I-obj
interview	OO
Mr.	B-per
Bakri	I-per
London	B-geo
al-Qaida	B-org
Osama	B-per
bin	I-per
Laden	I-per
Iran	B-gpe
U.S.	B-gpe
commander	OO
Washington	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Joint	B-org
Chiefs	I-org
of	I-org
Staff	I-org
Mike	B-per
Mullen	I-per
Sunday	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Admiral	B-per
Mullen	I-per
Iran	B-gpe
minister	OO
Brigadier	B-per
General	I-per
Ahmad	I-per
Vahidi	I-perO
Tuesday	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Tehran	B-gpe
United	B-gpe
States	I-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
Admiral	B-per
Mullen	I-per
Georgia	B-gpe
Iran	B-geo
President	B-per
Mikhail	I-per
Saakashvili	I-per
Friday	B-time
Iran	B-geo
Georgia	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
or	OO
latest	OO
Monday	B-time
Russian	B-gpe
Russian	B-gpe
Georgian	B-gpe
supplies	OO
Sunday	B-time
Georgia	B-gpe
Russian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Saakashvili	I-per
Iran	B-geo
Georgians	B-gpe
station	OO
Peru	B-gpe
President	OO
Alberto	B-per
Fujimori	I-perO
April	B-time
Peruvian	B-gpe
Tokyo	B-geo
Wednesday	B-timeO
Mr.	B-per
Fujimori	I-per
Si	B-org
Cumple	I-org
signature	OO
Japanese	B-gpe
Japan	B-geo
2000	B-timeO
Peru	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Fujimori	I-perO
Peru	B-geo
1990	B-time
2000	B-timeO
charges	OO
Tokyo	B-gpe
Lima	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
Sudan	B-geo
public	OO
Thursday	B-time
Sudanese	B-gpe
week	OO
capital	OO
Khartoum	B-geo
Sudanese	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
Khartoum	B-geo
Kenyan	B-gpe
Prophet	B-per
Muhammad	I-perO
Muslim	B-org
Kenyan	B-gpe
Friday	B-time
Danish	B-gpe
Nairobi	B-geoO
Danish	B-gpe
Friday	B-time
Middle	B-geo
East	I-geo
India	B-geoO
Pakistan	B-geoO
Afghanistan	B-geoO
Bangladesh	B-geoO
Malaysia	B-geoO
Venezuela	B-geo
France	B-geoO
Muslim	B-org
French	B-gpe
Council	B-org
Muslim	B-org
Faith	I-org
French	B-gpe
cartoons	OO
Prophet	B-per
Muhammad	I-per
Malaysian	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Abdullah	I-per
Ahmad	I-per
Badawi	I-per
Friday	B-time
Muslim	B-org
West	B-geo
China	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
China	B-geo
Shaanxi	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
surface	OO
Xinhua	B-org
mine	OO
Chinese	B-gpe
explosions	OO
floods	OO
India	B-org
and	I-org
Pakistan	I-org
January	B-time
security	OO
Kashmir	B-geo
January	B-time
17	I-time
January	B-time
2004	I-time
Islamabad	B-geo
Kashmir	B-geo
Pakistani	B-gpe
Kashmir	B-geo
India	B-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
Tuesday	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
Monday	B-timeO
Iraq	B-geo
Monday	B-timeO
Iraqi	B-gpe
Wael	B-per
al-Rubaei	I-per
Baghdad	B-geo
Iran	B-geo
Guardian	B-org
Council	I-org
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
U.N.	B-org
Security	I-org
Council	I-org
Saturday	B-time
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Ahmadinejad	I-per
Europe	B-gpe
Iran	B-gpe
August	B-timeO
Tehran	B-gpe
year	OO
Tehran	B-gpe
weapons	OO
Zambian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Levy	I-per
Mwanawasa	I-per
Information	B-per
Minister	I-per
Mike	I-per
Mulongoti	I-per
Thursday	B-time
President	B-per
Mwanawasa	I-per
Paris	B-geo
hospital	OO
Mr.	B-per
Mwanawasa	I-per
France	B-geo
Tuesday	B-time
Sunday	B-time
Egypt	B-geo
African	B-org
Union	I-org
Zimbabwe	B-geoO
Mr.	B-per
Mwanawasa	I-perO
Zimbabwean	B-gpe
President	B-per
Robert	I-per
Mugabe	I-perO
Harare	B-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Mwanawasa	I-per
Zambia	B-gpe
2002	B-time
Southern	B-org
African	I-org
Development	I-org
Community	I-org
U.S.	B-gpe
President	B-per
Barack	I-per
Obama	I-per
Gene	B-per
Sperling	I-per
National	B-org
Economic	I-org
Council	I-orgO
Sperling	B-per
President	B-per
Bill	I-per
Clinton	I-per
Lawrence	B-per
Summers	I-perO
Sperling	B-per
Obama	B-per
Treasury	B-per
Secretary	I-per
Timothy	I-per
Geithner	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Obama	I-per
Friday	B-time
Washington	B-geoO
D.C.	B-geo
Sperling	B-per
Obama	B-per
House	B-org
of	I-org
Representatives	I-orgO
2012	B-time
Thursday	B-timeO
Mr.	B-per
Obama	I-per
official	OO
William	B-per
Daley	I-perO
staff	OO
Rahm	B-per
Emmanuel	I-per
Bosnia-Herzegovina	B-gpe
Bosnian	B-gpe
Serb	I-gpe
1995	B-time
Bosnian	B-gpe
Srebrenica	B-geo
Dragan	B-per
Neskovic	I-per
Wednesday	B-time
Bijeljina	B-geo
Serb	B-gpe
July	B-time
1995	I-time
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Srebrenica	B-geo
World	B-event
War	I-event
II	I-event
U.N.	B-org
Hague	B-geo
Serbs	B-gpe
Bosnian	B-gpe
Serb	I-gpe
Radovan	B-per
Karadzic	I-per
there	OO
Bosnian	B-gpe
2005	B-time
China	B-geo
Xinhua	B-org
Shaanxi	B-geo
province	OO
Xinhua	B-org
unearthed	OO
Shaanxi	B-org
Provincial	I-org
Archaeological	I-org
Research	I-org
Institute	I-org
Neolithic	B-time
period	OO
New	B-time
Stone	I-time
Age	I-time
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Thailand	B-geo
Muslim	B-org
Philip	B-per
Alston	I-per
October	B-time
25	I-time
Thailand	B-geo
Thailand	B-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Alston	I-per
Meanwhile	OO
Thailand	B-gpe
King	B-per
Bhumibol	I-per
Adulyadej	I-per
January	B-time
Thailand	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinians	B-gpe
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
Friday	B-time
Gaza	B-geo
Israel	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinians	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
West	B-geo
Bank	I-geo
Nablus	B-geo
al-Aqsa	B-org
Martyrs	I-org
'	I-org
Brigades	I-orgO
Fatah	B-org
Party	I-org
Palestinian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
Hamas	B-org
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ismail	I-per
Haniyeh	I-per
Friday	B-time
Israeli	B-gpe
Nablus	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
Horn	B-geo
Africa	B-geo
Afghanistan	B-geo
Iraq	B-geo
Africa	B-geo
Major	B-per
General	I-per
Timothy	I-per
Ghormley	I-per
Africa	B-geo
General	B-per
Ghormley	I-per
Djibouti	B-geo
However	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Somalia	B-geoO
year	OO
Ethiopian	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Meles	I-per
Zenawi	I-per
al-Qaida	B-org
Somalia	B-gpe
capital	OO
Mogadishu	B-geo
Ugandan	B-gpe
Lord	B-org
's	I-org
Resistance	I-org
Army	I-org
International	B-org
Criminal	I-org
Court	I-org
James	B-per
Obita	I-perO
team	OO
VOA	B-org
Ugandan	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
Juba	B-geoO
Sudan	B-geo
request	OO
Uganda	B-geo
LRA	B-org
International	B-org
Criminal	I-org
Court	I-org
LRA	B-org
progress	OO
April	B-time
al-Qaida	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
Iraqi	B-gpe
Islamic	B-gpe
State	I-gpe
of	I-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
leader	OO
Abu	B-per
Omar	I-per
al-Baghdadi	I-perO
Iraqi	B-gpe
al-Baghdadi	B-per
Iraqi	B-gpe
Sunni	B-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
capital	OO
Baghdad	B-geo
United	B-gpe
States	I-gpe
Iraqi	B-gpe
leaders	OO
addition	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
General	B-per
Kevin	I-per
Bergner	I-per
al-Baghdadi	B-per
person	OO
Iraqi	B-gpe
al-Qaida	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
U.S.	B-gpe
Guantanamo	B-geo
Bay	I-geoO
Cuba	B-geo
Air	B-org
Force	I-org
Brigadier	B-per
General	I-per
Thomas	I-per
Hemingway	I-per
Wednesday	B-time
American	B-gpe
system	OO
enough	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Guantanamo	B-geoO
Center	B-org
for	I-org
Constitutional	I-org
Rights	I-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
Taleban	B-org
Kandahar	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
Army	B-org
Pakistani	B-gpe
Afghanistan	B-geo
Taleban	B-org
Afghan	B-gpe
forces	OO
Palestinian	B-gpe
Israel	B-geo
Sunday	B-timeO
Hamas	B-org
Popular	B-org
Resistance	I-org
Committees	I-org
March	B-time
Palestinian	B-org
Authority	I-org
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
al-Aqsa	B-org
Martyrs	I-org
Brigades	I-org
Islamic	B-org
Jihad	I-org
deal	OO
Israel	B-geo
development	OO
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
later	OO
Gaza	B-geo
Italian	B-gpe
Khan	B-geo
Younis	I-geoO
Iraq	B-geo
al-Qaida	B-org
Sunni	B-geo
Arab	I-geo
politician	OO
Adnan	B-per
al-Dulaymi	I-per
U.S.	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Green	B-geo
Zone	I-geoO
government	OO
Mr.	B-per
Dulaymi	I-per
Iraqi	B-gpe
Friday	B-timeO
Iraqi	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geoO
Sunday	B-time
Tal	B-geo
Afar	I-geoO
Saturday	B-timeO
U.S.	B-gpe
Iraqi	B-gpe
al-Qaida	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
Baghdad	B-geo
Kirkuk	B-geo
province	OO
Tarmiyah	B-geo
Judaidah	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Special	I-org
Forces	I-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
U.S.	B-gpe
Iraqi	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
Sadr	B-geo
City	I-geo
district	OO
Shi'ite	B-org
Moqtada	B-per
al-Sadr	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
Iraqi	B-gpe
Shi'ite	B-org
Sadr	B-geo
City	I-geo
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Zalinge	B-geoO
Sudan	B-geo
Darfur	B-geo
U.N.	B-org
Thursday	B-time
Friday	B-timeO
Ron	B-per
Redmond	I-per
Darfur	B-geo
Redmond	B-per
week	OO
North	B-geo
Darfur	I-geo
Sudan	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
Darfur	B-geo
U.N.	B-org
region	OO
people	OO
Iraq	B-gpe
ministers	OO
Sunni	B-org
Saddam	B-per
Hussein	I-per
However	OO
Sunni	B-org
Human	I-org
Rights	I-org
Hashem	B-per
Ashibli	I-per
post	OO
Sunni	B-gpe
Arab	I-gpeO
Saadoun	B-per
al-Dulaimi	I-perO
minister	OO
Ibrahim	B-per
Bahr	I-per
al-Uloum	I-per
filled	OO
Meanwhile	OO
Iraqi	B-gpe
Transportation	B-org
Ministry	I-org
Zoba	B-per
Yass	I-per
Baghdad	B-geo
Separately	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Sunday	B-time
al-Qaim	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
economy	OO
report	OO
Thursday	B-timeO
million	OO
Friday	B-time
insurance	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
2008	B-time
people	OO
children	OO
Monday	B-time
Pakistan	B-geo
Punjab	B-geo
Mian	B-geo
Channu	I-geo
blast	OO
houses	OO
Muslim	B-org
blast	OO
launchers	OO
grenades	OO
Pakistani	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Yusuf	I-per
Raza	I-per
Gilani	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
Luis	B-per
Posada	I-per
Carriles	I-perO
CIA	B-org
Cuba	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
Posada	B-per
Carriles	I-per
May	B-time
Mexico	B-geo
Posada	B-per
Carriles	I-per
Venezuela	B-geo
1976	B-time
Cuban	B-gpe
ago	OO
Venezuelan	B-gpe
May	B-timeO
U.S.	B-gpe
Venezuelan	B-gpe
arrest	OO
Cuban	B-gpe
Venezuelan	B-gpe
Pakistani	B-gpe
President	B-per
Pervez	I-per
Musharraf	I-per
Pakistanis	B-gpe
terrorism	OO
Pakistan	B-gpe
Thursday	B-timeO
General	B-per
Musharraf	I-per
printing	OO
material	OO
newspapers	OO
magazines	OO
pamphlets	OO
Pakistan	B-gpe
militancy	OO
schools	OO
General	B-per
Musharraf	I-per
Pakistan	B-geo
U.S.	B-gpe
procedures	OO
lists	OO
Americans	B-gpe
diseases	OO
changes	OO
U.S.	B-gpe
Centers	B-org
for	I-org
Disease	I-org
Control	I-orgO
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
CDC	B-org
U.S.	B-gpe
2003	B-time
SARS	OO
outbreak	OO
flu	OO
Asia	B-geo
2003	B-time
Pakistani	B-gpe
Shi'ite	B-org
Muslim	I-org
official	OO
Saud	B-per
Aziz	I-perO
Agha	B-per
Ziauddin	I-per
Gilgit	B-geo
January	B-time
Rawalpindi	B-geo
Sunni	B-org
Muslim	I-org
Lashkar-e-Jhangvi	I-org
Shi'ite	B-org
Pakistani	B-gpe
Shi'ite	B-org
Muslims	I-org
al-Qaida	B-org
Latvia	B-obj
Latgalians	B-orgO
Baltic	B-geo
Latvian	B-gpe
A.D.	B-time
Germans	B-gpeO
Poles	B-gpeO
Swedes	B-gpeO
finally	OO
Russians	B-gpe
Latvian	B-gpe
World	B-event
War	I-event
I	I-eventO
USSR	B-gpe
1940	B-time
US	B-gpe
Latvia	B-gpe
1991	B-time
Soviet	B-gpe
Union	I-gpe
Russian	B-gpe
1994	B-timeO
Russian	B-gpe
Moscow	B-gpe
Latvia	B-gpe
NATO	B-org
EU	B-org
2004	B-time
Bolivia	B-gpe
Latin	B-geo
America	I-geo
1980s	B-timeO
investment	OO
growth	OO
1990s	B-time
2003	B-time
-	I-time
5	I-time
instability	OO
tensions	OO
Bolivia	B-gpe
2005	B-timeO
2008	B-timeO
2009	B-time
Nevertheless	OO
Bolivia	B-gpe
South	B-geo
America	I-geo
2010	B-time
However	OO
Bolivian	B-gpe
Swazis	B-gpe
Africa	B-geo
British	B-gpe
Somali	B-gpe
Spanish	B-gpe
Spanish	B-gpe
Spain	B-geo
Spanish	B-gpe
Fernando	B-per
Andreu	I-per
Somali	B-gpe
Friday	B-time
Kenyan	B-gpe
Spain	B-geo
Spanish	B-gpe
Somalia	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
France	B-geo
Kenya	B-geo
Friday	B-time
China	B-org
Xinhua	B-org
China	B-org
Health	B-org
Ministry	I-org
China	B-org
Health	B-per
Minister	I-per
Gao	I-per
Qiang	I-per
Saturday	B-time
Norwegian	B-gpe
Svalbard	B-geo
Norway	B-gpe
Jens	B-per
Stoltenberg	I-per
Nobel-Prize	B-obj
Wangari	B-per
Maathai	I-per
Tuesday	B-time
Norwegian	B-gpe
9	B-time
Iraqi	B-gpe
Wednesday	B-time
Baghdad	B-geo
Iraq	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Abu	B-org
Musab	I-org
al-Zarqawi	B-per
al-Qaida	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
Australian	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
North	B-geo
Kirkuk	B-geo
Irbil	B-geo
Dohuk	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Hilla	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
Islamic	B-geo
Jihad	I-geo
Islamic	B-org
Jihad	I-org
Israel	B-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
Jabaliya	B-geo
Islamic	B-geo
Jihad	I-geo
Palestinians	B-gpe
Shahdi	B-geo
Mohanna	I-geo
Islamic	B-geo
Jihad	I-geo
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
Islamic	B-geo
Jihad	I-geo
Thursday	B-time
Israeli	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ariel	I-per
Sharon	I-per
Palestinian	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Mahmoud	B-per
Abbas	I-per
Afghan	B-gpe
Taliban	B-org
British	B-gpe
Reuters	B-org
Guardian	B-org
Afghans	B-gpe
Kabul	B-geo
May	B-time
29	I-time
Afghan	B-gpe
President	B-per
Hamid	I-per
Karzai	I-per
U.S.	B-gpe
Barack	B-per
Obama	I-per
Washington	B-geo
Russia	B-geo
Su-24	B-obj
Air	B-org
force	I-org
Thursday	B-time
Far	B-geo
East	I-geo
Khabarovsk	I-geo
Russian	B-gpe
Crimea	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Sevastopol	B-geo
Ukrainian	B-gpe
Russia	B-org
Sevastopol	B-geo
NATO	B-org
Wednesday	B-time
Ukraine	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Black	B-org
Sea	I-org
Sevastopol	B-geo
Ukraine	B-org
Russia	B-org
2017	B-time
Ukraine	B-geo
NATO	B-org
Moscow	B-org
Russia	B-geo
Egypt	B-gpe
Cairo	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
Muslim	B-org
Brotherhood	I-org
Egyptian	B-gpe
Cairo	B-geo
Cairo	B-geo
Egyptian	B-gpe
Brotherhood	B-org
Muslim	B-org
Brotherhood	I-org
Egypt	B-org
1954	B-time
Brotherhood	B-geo
Egypt	B-geo
Russia	B-geo
Monday	B-time
Russian	B-gpe
Topol-M	B-obj
Ivanov	B-per
Russia	B-org
Topol	B-obj
Topol	B-obj
Russian	B-gpe
1990s	B-time
Afghanistan	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
Kabul	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
eastern	B-geo
Afghanistan	I-geo
Khost	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
American	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
Arizona	B-geo
Minuteman	B-org
Project	I-org
U.S.	B-geo
Mexico	B-geo
James	B-per
Gilchrist	I-per
Minuteman	B-org
U.S.	B-geo
Washington	B-org
Times	I-org
Mara	B-geo
Salvatrucha	I-geo
MS-13	B-geo
Arizona	B-geo
Tombstone	B-time
Friday	I-time
National	B-org
Alliance	I-org
for	I-org
Human	I-org
Rights	I-org
Minuteman	B-org
Project	I-org
Arizona	B-geo
MS-13	B-geo
Central	B-org
and	I-org
South	I-org
America	I-org
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
World	B-org
Bank	I-org
Colombia	B-geo
Thursday	B-time
Colombia	B-geo
Bank	B-org
Colombia	B-org
El	B-org
Salvador	I-org
27	B-time
Red	B-org
Solidaria	I-org
Salvadorans	B-gpe
Italian	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Silvio	B-per
Berlusconi	I-per
Sunday	B-time
Tuesday	B-time
Mr.	B-per
Berlusconi	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Berlusconi	I-per
Romano	B-per
Prodi	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Berlusconi	I-per
Prodi	B-per
Prodi	B-per
Sunday	B-time
Monday	B-time
Iraqi	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
Shi'ite	B-geo
Muslim	I-geo
New	B-org
Baghdad	I-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
Shi'ite	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
Karbala	B-geo
Ashura	B-event
each	B-time
Prophet	B-per
Muhammad	I-per
Friday	B-time
eastern	B-geo
Baghdad	I-geo
Sadr	B-geo
City	I-geo
Mosul	B-geo
Christmas	B-event
America	B-geo
Moses	B-per
Bittok	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Bittok	I-per
Kenya	B-geo
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
Iowa	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Mr.	B-per
Bittok	I-per
America	B-geo
Japanese	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
North	B-geo
Korea	B-gpe
Pyongyang	B-gpe
Shinzo	B-per
Abe	I-per
Japan	B-gpe
Liberal	B-org
Democratic	I-org
Party	I-org
Sunday	B-time
Tokyo	B-gpe
North	B-geo
Korea	B-gpe
U.S.	B-gpe
North	B-geo
Korea	B-gpe
Kilju	B-geo
Fox	B-org
News	I-org
Sunday	B-time
U.S.	B-gpe
National	B-org
Security	I-org
Adviser	I-org
Stephen	B-per
Hadley	I-per
Washington	B-gpe
North	B-geo
Korean	B-gpe
North	B-geo
Korea	B-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Monday	B-time
Green	B-org
Zone	I-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
U.S.	B-geo
Obeidi	B-per
Syrian	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
Iraqi	B-gpe
Euphrates	B-geo
River	I-geo
Sunday	B-time
Iraq	B-geo
Sunni	B-geo
Arab	I-geo
European	B-org
Union	I-org
Health	I-org
Markos	B-per
Kypriano	I-per
EU	B-org
120	B-time
EU	B-org
Beijing	B-geo
Tuesday	B-time
World	B-org
Bank	I-org
and	I-org
World	I-org
Health	I-org
Organization	I-org
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
Wednesday	B-time
Swiss	B-gpe
Roche	B-per
Tamiflu	B-geo
World	B-org
Health	I-org
Organization	I-org
Margaret	B-per
Chan	I-per
Inter-American	B-org
Development	I-org
Bank	I-org
Haitian	B-gpe
2006	B-time
Tuesday	B-time
Haiti	B-geo
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
Haitian	B-gpe
Boston	B-geo
Miami	B-geo
New~York	B-geo
Canada	B-geo
France	B-org
Bahamas	B-geo
Ukraine	B-geo
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Yury	I-per
Yekhanurov	I-per
Russia	B-org
from	B-time
Saturday	I-time
to	I-time
Wednesday	I-time
Mr.	B-per
Yekhanurov	B-org
Ukraine	B-org
Russia	B-org
January	B-time
4	I-time
three-day	B-time
Russian	B-gpe
Ukraine	B-geo
Ukraine	B-geo
Chinese	B-gpe
Xinhua	B-org
State	B-org
Council	I-org
Friday	B-time
first	B-time
quarter	I-time
China	B-geo
first	B-time
quarter	I-time
2006	B-time
Chinese	B-gpe
two	B-time
end	B-time
of	I-time
March	I-time
Burma	B-gpe
Burmese	B-gpe
Japanese	B-gpe
Burma	B-org
Media	I-org
Association	I-org
two	B-time
of	B-time
detention	I-time
Monday	B-time
Rangoon	B-geo
Korean	B-gpe
Aung	B-org
Shwe	I-org
Oo	I-org
Daw	B-per
Sint	I-per
Sint	I-per
Aung	I-per
Nippon	B-org
News	I-org
Network	I-org
's	I-org
Bangkok	I-org
Indian	B-geo
Ocean	I-geo
December	B-time
26	I-time
British	B-gpe
HMS	B-per
Scott	I-per
Indonesia	B-geo
Sumatra	B-geo
Island	I-geo
January	B-time
House	B-org
committee-chairman	I-org
Ohio	B-gpe
Representative	B-org
Bob	B-per
Ney	I-per
House	B-org
recent	B-time
Sunday	B-time
House	B-org
Administration	I-org
Committee	I-org
Ney	B-per
Jack	B-per
Abramoff	I-per
Abramoff	B-per
Ney	B-per
Texas	B-gpe
Tom	B-per
DeLay	I-per
House	B-org
Majority	I-org
Leader	I-org
DeLay	B-per
Abramoff	B-per
Abramoff	B-per
July	B-time
21	I-time
London	B-geo
Italy	B-geo
Britain	B-geo
Hamdi	B-per
Issac	I-per
Osman	B-per
Hussain	I-per
Rome	B-geo
Ciampino	B-geo
midday	B-time
Thursday	I-time
London	B-geo
Italian	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
Rome	B-geo
July	B-time
21	I-time
London	B-geo
two	B-time
British	B-gpe
Hamdi	B-per
Issac	I-per
Italy	B-geo
September	B-time
13	I-time
Mississippi	B-geo
River	I-geo
Illinois	B-geo
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
Army	B-org
Corps	I-org
of	I-org
Engineers	I-org
U.S.	B-geo
Central	B-geo
U.S.	I-geo
Iowa	B-geo
National	B-org
Guard	I-org
Iowa	B-org
White	B-org
House	I-org
Tuesday	B-time
U.S.	B-org
President	B-per
George	I-per
Bush	I-per
Iowa	B-geo
Thursday	B-time
U.S.	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
General	B-per
Iraq	B-geo
Reconstruction	I-geo
fourth	B-time
quarter	I-time
of	I-time
2004	I-time
Iraq	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Congress	I-org
U.S.	B-org
Labor	I-org
Department	I-org
U.S.	B-org
Chilean	B-gpe
Augusto	B-per
Pinochet	I-per
Victor	B-per
Montiglio	I-per
General	B-org
Pinochet	I-org
of	B-time
his	I-time
1973	I-time
to	I-time
1990	I-time
Operation	B-per
Colombo	I-per
Mr.	B-per
Montiglio	I-per
Thursday	B-time
Manuel	B-per
Contreras	I-per
Pinochet	B-org
two	B-time
General	B-org
Pinochet	I-org
Friday	B-time
Wednesday	B-time
South	B-org
American	I-org
Mercosur	B-org
Venezuela	B-geo
Venezuela	B-org
Argentina	B-org
Brazil	B-org
Paraguay	B-org
Uruguay	B-org
Tuesday	B-time
Venezuela	B-org
Bolivian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Evo	I-per
Morales	I-per
Brazilian	B-gpe
Luiz	B-per
Inacio	I-per
Lula	I-per
da	I-per
Silva	I-per
Brazil	B-geo
Bolivia	B-geo
Mercosur	B-geo
1991	B-time
Paraguay	B-org
President	B-per
Nicanor	I-per
Duarte	I-per
Brazil	B-org
Argentina	B-org
Indonesia	B-geo
Aceh	B-geo
midnight	B-time
Saturday	I-time
1657	B-time
UTC	I-time
Indian	B-geo
Ocean	I-geo
Banda	B-geo
Aceh	I-geo
Aceh	B-geo
December	B-time
26	I-time
U.S.	B-org
Geological	I-org
Survey	I-org
Indian	B-geo
Ocean	I-geo
Aceh	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
President	B-per
Bush	I-per
Social	B-org
Security	I-org
70th	B-time
anniversary	I-time
Senator	B-per
John	I-per
Kerry	I-per
Spanish	B-obj
Saturday	B-time
Senator	B-per
Ken	I-per
Salazar	I-per
Colorado	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
President	B-per
Bush	I-per
few	B-time
decades	I-time
Social	B-org
Security	I-org
African	B-gpe
Gulf	B-geo
of	I-geo
Aden	I-geo
Yemen	B-geo
Yemeni	B-gpe
Somalia	B-geo
Somalians	B-per
Somalia	B-geo
Yemeni	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
High	I-org
Commissioner	I-org
for	I-org
Refugees	I-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
1990s	B-time
Abdul	B-org
Saboor	I-org
Farid	I-org
Wednesday	B-time
Kabul	B-org
Mr.	B-per
Farid	I-per
Afghanistan	B-geo
one	B-time
1992	B-time
Afghan	B-gpe
Thursday	B-time
Kabul	B-org
Taleban	B-org
British	B-gpe
British	B-gpe
Afghanistan	B-geo
NATO	B-org
Taleban	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
Baghdad	B-geo
Baquba	B-geo
Balad	B-per
Ruz	I-per
Saturday	B-time
U.S.	B-geo
Baiji	B-geo
Iraq	B-geo
Ibrahim	B-per
Ali	I-per
al-Nuimei	I-per
Kirkuk	B-geo
Saddam	B-per
Hussein	I-per
Tuesday	B-time
Western	B-org
diplomat	I-org
Baathist	B-org
United	B-org
States	I-org
Government	I-org
Wednesday	B-time
May	B-time
14	I-time
Endangered	B-obj
Species	I-obj
Act	I-obj
Bush	B-per
Paul	B-per
Sisco	I-per
Iranian	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
International	I-org
Atomic	I-org
Energy	I-org
Agency	I-org
Iran	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
Iranian	B-gpe
August	B-time
6	I-time
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Iran	B-org
Arak	B-geo
U.N.	B-org
Security	I-org
Council	I-org
Iran	B-org
United	B-org
States	I-org
Iran	B-org
Iran	B-org
Iraq	B-geo
U.S.	B-geo
Donald	B-per
Rumsfeld	I-per
American	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
Shi'ite	B-org
Balad	B-geo
Ruz	I-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Abu	B-per
Musab	I-per
al-Zarqawi	I-per
American	B-gpe
western	B-geo
Baghdad	I-geo
Mr.	B-per
Rumsfeld	I-per
U.S.	B-org
Mosul	B-geo
Baghdad	B-geo
Iraqi	B-org
Iraqi	B-org
Prime	B-per
Iyad	B-per
Allawi	I-per
Nigerian	B-gpe
Polish	B-gpe
Niger	B-gpe
Polish	B-gpe
Sunday	B-time
Thursday	B-time
Warri	B-geo
oil-rich	B-org
Niger	B-gpe
Delta	B-org
Nigeria	B-org
almost	B-time
U.S.	B-org
Treasury	I-org
Palestinian	B-gpe
Hamas	B-org
Sunday	B-time
KindHearts	B-org
Hamas	B-org
U.S.	B-org
2001	B-time
KindHearts	B-org
Web	B-obj
KindHearts	B-org
Hamas	B-org
Palestinian	B-gpe
U.S.	B-org
Israel	B-org
Israeli	B-gpe
China	B-geo
Beijing	B-geo
Olympic	B-event
Games	I-event
China	B-geo
Olympic	B-event
Liu	B-per
Shaowu	I-per
Wednesday	B-time
Athens	B-org
Greece	B-geo
Olympic	B-event
Games	I-event
2004	B-time
International	B-org
Olympic	I-org
Committee	I-org
Olympic	B-event
Olympic	B-event
China	B-org
Tibet	B-geo
International	B-org
Obesity	I-org
Task	I-org
Force	I-org
VOA	B-org
Carol	B-per
Pearson	I-per
Australian	B-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
World	B-org
Vision	I-org
Australia	I-org
Tim	B-per
Costello	I-per
Iraq	B-geo
Iraq	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Costello	I-per
Iraq	B-geo
Margaret	B-per
Hassan	I-per
Iraqi	B-org
Mohammed	B-per
Hushiar	I-per
September	B-time
Mosul	B-geo
Bush	B-per
Iraqi	B-gpe
New	B-org
York	I-org
Times	I-org
Secretary	B-per
State	B-per
Condoleezza	I-per
Rice	I-per
Iraq	B-org
President	B-per
Jalal	I-per
Talabani	I-per
Friday	B-time
Ms.	B-per
Rice	I-per
Vice	B-per
President	I-per
Dick	I-per
Cheney	I-per
White	B-org
House	I-org
Adil	B-per
Abdul	I-per
Mahdi	I-per
Shi'ite	B-org
Iraqi	B-gpe
U.S.	B-geo
Iraqis	B-gpe
American	B-gpe
Baghdad	B-geo
Iraqi	B-org
Iraqis	B-gpe
Israeli	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ehud	I-per
Olmert	I-per
Palestinian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Mahmoud	I-per
Abbas	I-per
Wednesday	B-time
Jerusalem	B-geo
Palestinian	B-gpe
Saeb	B-per
Erekat	I-per
Israeli	B-gpe
Palestinian	B-gpe
Mr.	B-per
Olmert	I-per
between	B-time
Mr.	B-per
Olmert	I-per
Kadima	B-org
Party	I-org
September	B-time
November	B-time
's	B-time
end	I-time
Afghanistan	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
Taleban	B-org
Taleban	B-org
Thursday	B-time
Chakul	B-geo
Helmand	B-geo
Later	B-time
Taleban	B-org
U.S.	B-org
Taleban	B-org
Thursday	B-time
U.S.	B-org
Khost	B-geo
Afghan	B-gpe
Taleban	B-org
Afghan	B-gpe
Britain	B-geo
Iran	B-geo
Sunday	B-time
Conservative	B-org
Party	I-org
British	B-gpe
Iraq	B-geo
Afghanistan	B-geo
Iran	B-geo
13	B-time
British	B-gpe
Monday	B-time
Iran	B-geo
U.S.	B-geo
California	B-geo
Santa	B-geo
Barbara	I-geo
Saturday	B-time
morning	I-time
Friday	B-time
May	B-time
5	I-time
Iraqi	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Nouri	B-per
al-Maliki	I-per
Saddam	B-geo
Hussein	I-geo
Saddam	B-geo
Moqtada	B-geo
Saddam	B-geo
Saddam	B-geo
Sunni	B-geo
Arab	I-geo
Tuesday	B-time
Sunni	B-geo
Arab	I-geo
Saddam	B-geo
Afghanistan	B-geo
Nuristan	B-geo
Province	I-geo
Afghans	B-gpe
in	B-time
Kamdesh	B-time
Nuristan	B-geo
Province	I-geo
Afghans	B-gpe
More	B-time
than	I-time
three	I-time
U.S.-led	B-time
coalition	I-time
Taleban	B-org
Afghanistan	B-org
September	B-time
parliamentary	I-time
vote	I-time
Kandahar	B-geo
Province	I-geo
Russian	B-gpe
Mstislav	B-per
Rostropovich	I-per
80th	B-time
birthday	I-time
celebration	I-time
Moscow	B-geo
second	B-time
time	I-time
Thursday	B-time
February	B-time
Russian	B-gpe
Russian	B-gpe
President	B-per
Vladimir	I-per
Putin	I-per
Rostropovich	B-per
Rostropovich	B-per
Galina	B-per
Vishnevskaya	I-per
Soviet	B-geo
Union	I-geo
1974	B-time
Russia	B-geo
Soviet	B-geo
Union	I-geo
U.S.	B-org
Google	B-org
California	B-geo
Internet	B-obj
Mountain	B-geo
View	I-geo
California	B-geo
California	B-geo
Google	B-org
Israeli	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Minister	I-per
Ariel	I-per
Sharon	I-per
Gaza	B-geo
Strip	I-geo
West	B-org
Bank	I-org
enclaves	I-org
Monday	B-time
Gaza	B-geo
Gaza	B-geo
West	B-geo
Bank	I-geo
July	B-time
starting	I-time
date	I-time
Israeli	B-gpe
West	B-org
Bank	I-org
Palestinian	B-gpe
Jenin	B-geo
today	B-time
Islamic	B-geo
Jihad	I-geo
Israeli	B-gpe
American	B-gpe
Andre	B-per
Agassi	I-per
Delray	B-event
Beach	I-event
International	I-event
Florida	B-geo
Friday	B-time
Spain	B-gpe
Guillermo	B-per
Garcia-Lopez	I-per
Spaniard	B-gpe
Xavier	B-per
Malisse	I-per
Belgium	B-gpe
Malisse	B-per
Florian	B-per
Mayer	I-per
Germany	B-gpe
Tommy	B-per
Haas	I-per
Germany	B-gpe
Luxembourg	B-gpe
Gilles	B-per
Muller	I-per
Haas	B-per
American	B-gpe
Vince	B-per
Spadea	I-per
Lee	B-per
Hyung-taik	I-per
South	B-geo
Korea	I-geo
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Syrian	B-gpe
Lebanese	B-gpe
Prime	B-per
Rafik	B-per
Hariri	I-per
Syrian	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
Vienna	B-geo
Wednesday	B-time
Austrian	B-gpe
Sunday	B-time
Damascus	B-org
Syria	B-geo
Syria	B-org
February	B-time
14	I-time
Beirut	B-geo
Mr.	B-per
Hariri	I-per
U.N.	B-org
October	B-time
Syrian	B-gpe
Lebanese	B-gpe
U.N.	B-org
Security	I-org
Council	I-org
Syria	B-org
Syria	B-org
Lebanon	B-geo
U.S.	B-org
Senator	B-per
-	B-org
Hillary	B-per
Rodham	I-per
Clinton	I-per
Iowa	B-geo
Washington	B-geo
D.C.	B-geo
Senator	B-per
Clinton	I-per
New	B-geo
York	I-geo
2006	B-time
Iowa	B-geo
2008	B-time
U.S.	B-geo
Iowa	B-geo
Mrs.	B-per
Clinton	I-per
2000	B-time
Senate	B-org
Los	B-geo
Angeles	I-geo
Hollywood	B-geo
Mrs.	B-per
Clinton	I-per
Burmese	B-gpe
Aung	B-per
San	I-per
Suu	I-per
Kyi	I-per
Saturday	B-time
United	B-org
Nations	I-org
Aung	B-per
San	I-per
Suu	I-per
Kyi	I-per
Saturday	B-time
Rangoon	B-geo
Vijay	B-per
Nambiar	I-per
U.N.	B-per
Secretary-General	B-org
Ban	B-per
Ki-moon	I-per
Nobel	B-obj
release	B-time
November	I-time
13	I-time
from	I-time
more	I-time
than	I-time
seven	I-time
Burma	B-geo
Nambiar	B-per
Saturday	B-time
Burma	B-org
Pakistani	B-gpe
al-Qaida	B-org
Afghan	B-gpe
Monday	B-time
Peshawar	B-geo
Pakistani	B-org
al-Qaida	B-org
North	B-geo
Waziristan	I-geo
Afghanistan	B-geo
Muhsin	B-per
Musa	I-per
Matwali	I-per
Atwah	I-per
1998	B-time
U.S.	B-org
Kenya	B-geo
Tanzania	B-geo
United	B-geo
States	I-geo
eastern	B-geo
Sudan	I-geo
Eritrea	B-geo
Eastern	B-org
Front	I-org
Friday	B-time
Thursday	B-time
Barka	B-geo
Valley	I-geo
Tokar	B-geo
Port	B-per
Sudan	B-gpe
Red	B-geo
Sea	I-geo
French	B-gpe
Friday	B-time
Tokar	B-geo
Sudanese	B-gpe
February	B-time
Eastern	B-org
Front	I-org
Benedict	B-per
XVI	I-per
Italian	B-gpe
L'Aquilla	B-geo
Italian	B-gpe
Tuesday	B-time
L'Aquilla	B-geo
13th	B-time
century	I-time
Santa	B-geo
Maria	I-geo
di	I-geo
Collemaggio	I-geo
basilica	I-geo
Benedict	B-per
Onna	B-geo
April	B-time
6	I-time
Abruzzo	B-geo
Italian	B-gpe
U.S.	B-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
Taleban	B-org
six	B-time
to	I-time
nine	I-time
Lieutenant	B-per
General	I-per
David	I-per
Barno	I-per
Saturday	B-time
Taleban	B-org
Afghanistan	B-geo
General	B-per
Barno	I-per
Taleban	B-org
Afghanistan	B-gpe
September	B-time
18	I-time
one	B-time
Germany	B-geo
Saturday	B-time
Berlin	B-org
Wall	I-org
Germany	B-geo
Helmut	B-per
Kohl	I-per
U.S.	B-geo
George	B-per
Herbert	I-per
Walker	I-per
Bush	I-per
Mikhail	B-per
Gorbachev	I-per
Berlin	B-geo
Germany	B-geo
Chancellor	B-per
Kohl	I-per
Germany	B-geo
Germans	B-gpe
II	B-event
Germany	B-geo
1961	B-time
Iron	B-org
Curtain	I-org
democratic	B-geo
West	I-geo
November	B-time
9	I-time
